statisticssolutions.com 2008-05-19

# DNATube.com Scientific Video Site

### Privacy Policy 

By registering, you will open an account at Dnatube.com. Your data will be stored Dnatube.com database. Your data is always protected by our Privacy Policy and will not be shared . Dnatube.com affiliates use your data to administer your account, provide information of interest to you, and to communicate with you. You may opt out of receiving marketing materials by changing your account preferences. More information about how EA uses your data and your related rights can be found in our Privacy Policy below. By registering, you agree Dnatube.com may process your data in accordance with the following Privacy Policy and that you will abide by Terms & Conditions below.

I. DNATUBE ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY  
Dnatube respect the privacy rights of our online visitors and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected about you. We have adopted a corporate wide Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store and use the information you provide online. Whenever you visit a web site, you can expect to be notified of: What personal information may be collected and by what means Whether information is collected from children aged 12 and under Who, if anyone, is collecting your personal information How this information may be used, including, who - if anyone - it might be shared with The consequences - if any - resulting from your refusal to provide personal information How you can access and, if necessary, change the personal information a company maintains How a company ensures data security, quality, and integrity Where and how to ask questions or file complaints If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding our privacy statement or policies, please contact the Privacy Policy Administrator by e-mail ( admin@dnatube.com ) . 

For Terms of conditions: [click here! ](http://www.dnatube.com/terms.php)
